http://www.ucbi.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Click for our most recent information on:     COVID-19  |  Branch Status  |  PPP Forgiveness
1-800-UCBANK1
Or (1-800-822-2651)
Facts
WHAT DOES UNITED COMMUNITY BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Account balances and payment history
Credit history and Employment information
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons United Community Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does United Community Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
What we do
How does United Community Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does United Community Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Apply for a loan or give us your income information
Open an account or make deposits or withdrawals from your account
Use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Our affiliates include others, such as Our Mortgage Company and Advisory Services.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
United Community Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include Credit Card Companies
